https://www.osmre.gov/lrg/privacy.shtm

AMDTreat
Appalachian Regional Reforestation Initiative (ARRI)
Applicant Violator System (AVS)
Coal Reclamation Fee Report
e-AMLIS
GeoMine
National Mine Map Repository (NMMR)
Reg-8 Oversight Database (ODocs)
Technical Information and Professional Services (TIPS)
Contacts
How Do I?
DOI Manual Sections
on the Privacy Act (383 DM 1-15)
DOI Bureau Program Responsibilities
(383 DM 3)
DOI Privacy Act Regulations on Contracts (43 CFR 2.53)
OSMRE FOIA Program
OSMRE Privacy Impact Assessments (PIAs)
For More Information:
Web Privacy Policy and Important Notices
How we handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website depends upon what you do when visiting our site.
OSMRE is committed to protecting any information collected directly from you to the greatest extent possible and publishes notices about its record systems that contain personally identifiable information in the Federal
Register.
OSMRE Privacy Policy
This
notice provides OSMRE's policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of
any information collected via our website. We do not obtain personally identifying
information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide such
information to us. For website management, information is collected for
statistical purposes. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any
information we receive with any other program, organization, or outside
parties. OSMRE does not collect information for commercial marketing purposes.
Automatically
Collected Information
If you read
or download information such as brochures, reports, or press releases, we
collect and store only the following information about your visit:
The
name of the Internet domain from which you are accessing our website (for
example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or
"yourschool.edu" if you are connecting from a university's domain);
The
date and time you access our site;
The
Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site; and
The
pages you visit and the information you request.
This information does not identify you personally; it is not stored in any
particular fashion, but is part of a systems log file used internally for site
management purposes. This information is primarily collected to create summary
statistics which are used for such purposes as assessing what information is of
most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and
identifying system performance or problem areas. We use the information we
collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site
and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
Personal Information You Provide to OSMRE
You may
decide to send us personally identifying information in an e-mail containing a
complaint, requesting printed materials be mailed to you, or completing a
Citizen Request for Inspection of an Active Coal Mine form. We use personally identifying
information from you only to respond to your message and to help us get you the
information or services you have requested.
Any information that we collect via a questionnaire or form may be subject to
disclosure but will be handled in accordance with the requirements of the
Privacy Act, Freedom of Information Act, and the Surface Mining Control and
Reclamation Act to ensure the greatest protection of personal privacy in the
face of any required disclosure.
Remember: e-mail isn't necessarily secure. You should never send sensitive
or personal information like your Social Security Number in an e-mail. Instead,
use postal mail or secure websites to transmit sensitive information.
We may transfer personal information to a third party only in the following cases:
To a bank or United States Department of the Treasury account, which must receive
payment for a transaction that you initiated;
To a company that is contracted to assist us with specific services, including
electronic commerce or donations, and which agrees not to sell or use personal
information for other purposes;
To legal authorities if we suspect that you are attempting to change or otherwise
damage this website, or you are using it in violation of Federal or local laws;
or
To Congress or a court in response to a subpoena.
Disclaimer on OSMRE Links to Other Sites
OSMRE
may link to websites created and maintained by other Federal agencies and/or
private organizations. The presence of a link is not an OSMRE endorsement of the
website. When you follow a link to any outside website, you are leaving OSMRE and
are subject to the privacy and security policies of the sponsor(s) of the
outside website.OSMRE is not responsible
for the information collection practices of non-OSMRE websites.
Privacy
Impact Assessments
For a list of approved public OSMRE Privacy Impact Assessments (PIAs), click here.
on the Privacy Act (383 DM 1-15)
DOI Bureau Program Responsibilities
(383 DM 3)
DOI Privacy Act Regulations on Contracts (43 CFR 2.53)
OSMRE FOIA Program
Page Last Modified/Reviewed:
AML Inventory System (e-AMLIS)
Coal CombustionResidues (CCRs)
Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement, 1849 C Street NW, Washington, DC 20240
